<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<packageId>RunningBugs.WorldMapEditor</packageId>
	<name>世界地图编辑器 World Map Editor</name>
	<author>RunningBugs</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>

	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>

	<incompatibleWith>
		<!-- <li>username.modname</li> -->
	</incompatibleWith>

	<loadAfter>
		<!-- <li>username.modname</li> -->
	</loadAfter>

	<description>
世界地图编辑器 World Map Editor

本模组让玩家在进入游戏后（非创建游戏时）可以在世界地图上编辑地块。可以设置地块的生物群落、丘陵度、定居点等。
This mod allows players to edit map tiles on the world map after entering the game (not when creating a new game). You can set the biome, hilliness, and settlements of the map tiles.

目前的实现方法在有性能问题，但是可以通过关闭编辑器来解决。模组的源代码附在MOD中，并且已上传至GitHub，希望有大神提出优化建议或者pull request。
The current implementation has performance issues, but they can be resolved by closing the editor. The source code of the mod is included in the mod and has been uploaded to GitHub. Any suggestions for optimization or pull requests are welcome.

启用时，此模组会在每个地块上创建一个隐形的世界对象，这会显著影响性能。关闭时，这些对象会被移除，恢复正常性能。
When enabled, this mod creates an invisible world object on each map tile, which can significantly impact performance. When disabled, these objects are removed, restoring normal performance.

在保存之前，世界对象会自动移除，以保持较小的存档文件。
The world objects are automatically removed before saving to keep the save file size small.

提示：如果您在世界地图上遇到性能问题，请尝试将编辑器打开然后关闭，以移除这些对象。
Tip: If you experience performance issues on the world map, try toggling the editor on and then off to remove the objects.

启用时，世界地图编辑器支持拖拽选择，但性能会非常差。请尽可能放大视角以获得最佳性能。您最多可同时选择80个地块。
When on, World Map Editor supports drag-selection, but the performance would be really really bad. Please zoom in your camera as close as possible to get best performance. You can select 80 tiles at the same time.

</description>
</ModMetaData>
