<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Apparel_Phoenix_Feather_Bracelet.label>Phoenix Feather Bracelet</Apparel_Phoenix_Feather_Bracelet.label>
  <Apparel_Phoenix_Feather_Bracelet.description>A bracelet containing phoenix feathers. Provides fire protection and fire resistance.</Apparel_Phoenix_Feather_Bracelet.description>


  <Apparel_void_spirit_necklace.label>Void spirit necklace</Apparel_void_spirit_necklace.label>
  <Apparel_void_spirit_necklace.description>A necklace of void spirits flowing from a purple artifact. Because it amplifies the wearer's ability for psychic powers, most of the wearers are people related to psychic powers.</Apparel_void_spirit_necklace.description>


  <Apparel_blood_amplifying_device.label>Blood amplification chip</Apparel_blood_amplifying_device.label>
  <Apparel_blood_amplifying_device.description>A type of blood chip that ancient sanguophages attach to their arms to reduce blood flow. Increases Blood Efficiency while equipped.</Apparel_blood_amplifying_device.description>


  <Apparel_mine_hat.label>Mental stability hat</Apparel_mine_hat.label>
  <Apparel_mine_hat.description>A kind of wizard-shaped hat worn by hakuro demons. It looks normal with a costume that looks like a wizard's hat, but it has a spirit stone inserted to soothe the inner spirit.</Apparel_mine_hat.description>

  <Apparel_mine_Cape.label>Mental Stability cloak</Apparel_mine_Cape.label>
  <Apparel_mine_Cape.description>It is a mental stabilization cloak worn by white wolf demons.\n\nIt looks like a normal cloak, but it is equipped with a shield to protect the owner from several shots and stabilizing the inner spirit with the spirit stone.</Apparel_mine_Cape.description>

  <Apparel_gemstone_necklace.label>Mental stability gemstone necklace</Apparel_gemstone_necklace.label>
  <Apparel_gemstone_necklace.description>It is a magic stone necklace made by gnawing a spirit stone. When worn, it stabilizes the inner spirit even though it is small amount, and makes it possible to use supernatural powers efficiently.</Apparel_gemstone_necklace.description>

  <Apparel_knight_mental_stability_helmet.label>Nova Mental Stability Helmet</Apparel_knight_mental_stability_helmet.label>
  <Apparel_knight_mental_stability_helmet.description>The Nova Knight Armor Mental Stability Helmet is a helmet made by hakuro demons to stabilize their minds. It is a helmet designed to reduce the level of mental blockage from the demon gene, and is mainly worn by demons.</Apparel_knight_mental_stability_helmet.description>

  <Apparel_Mental_Heavy_Cloak.label>Mind stabilizing heavy armored cloak</Apparel_Mental_Heavy_Cloak.label>
  <Apparel_Mental_Heavy_Cloak.description>A cloak made of solid iron and lelilel cloth.\n\nUnlike other cloaks, it is made for combat. It protects itself from bullets with a bidirectional cloak, with a built-in protective shield protects the owner.</Apparel_Mental_Heavy_Cloak.description>

  <Apparel_Mental_Heavy_PowerArmor.label>mental stabilization heavy power armor</Apparel_Mental_Heavy_PowerArmor.label>
  <Apparel_Mental_Heavy_PowerArmor.description>It is a heavy armor worn by elite combat magicians of Hakuro.\n\nIt is a power armor that combines a power armor type that you have seen elsewhere and a magic heavy armor cloak.</Apparel_Mental_Heavy_PowerArmor.description>

  <Apparel_TerraPowerArmor.label>heavy terra power armor </Apparel_TerraPowerArmor.label>
  <Apparel_TerraPowerArmor.description>It is a Terra power armor with heavy armor-level defense.\n\nIt is a power armor with solid defense that can advance while being hit by numerous attacks. This armor is mainly used by royal guards or vanguards, it enhances solid defense and the user's survivability.</Apparel_TerraPowerArmor.description>

  <Apparel_Terra_Combat_Helmet.label>heavy terra power helmet</Apparel_Terra_Combat_Helmet.label>
  <Apparel_Terra_Combat_Helmet.description>A heavy armor helmet with high hard defense. There is a built-in combat auxiliary control system and a device to prevent mental sensitivity in preparation for mental attacks.</Apparel_Terra_Combat_Helmet.description>

  <Apparel_feather_mine_hat.label>Mental Stabilization Battle Cap</Apparel_feather_mine_hat.label>
  <Apparel_feather_mine_hat.description>With the White Rang Combat Wizard Hat, the accuracy rate for long and medium ranges has decreased, but the combat power for short ranges has increased.</Apparel_feather_mine_hat.description>

  <Apparel_monarchy_mine_hat.label>mind king wizard hat</Apparel_monarchy_mine_hat.label>
  <Apparel_monarchy_mine_hat.description>A hat worn by royal mages.</Apparel_monarchy_mine_hat.description>


</LanguageData>