<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Moonlight_table.label>Moonlight workbench</Moonlight_table.label>
  <Moonlight_table.description>It is a mechanical workbench that manufactures weapons named moonlight.</Moonlight_table.description>

  <nano_machine_Fabrication.label>Nanomachine large workbench</nano_machine_Fabrication.label>
  <nano_machine_Fabrication.description>It is a kind of large workbench that uses nanomaterials to create equipment or weapons from various materials.</nano_machine_Fabrication.description>

  <nanomachine_ballast.label>Nanomachine assist system</nanomachine_ballast.label>
  <nanomachine_ballast.description>As a kind of device that analyzes the composition of materials, nanomachines assist large work benches to increase manufacturing efficiency.</nanomachine_ballast.description>

  <Nanomachined_Stability_Sensor.label>Nanomachined stabilizer</Nanomachined_Stability_Sensor.label>
  <Nanomachined_Stability_Sensor.description>A supplementary energy box that stabilizes nanomachines on a large nanomachine workbench.</Nanomachined_Stability_Sensor.description>

  <Mechdrone_Gestator.label>Drone production facility</Mechdrone_Gestator.label>
  <Mechdrone_Gestator.description>An incubation building that produces Overwatch drones. It looks like a facility used by mecha nighters, but only used to create and reanimate drones.</Mechdrone_Gestator.description>

  <Overwatch_Forward_Receiving_Facility.label>Overwatch Forward Receiving Facility</Overwatch_Forward_Receiving_Facility.label>
  <Overwatch_Forward_Receiving_Facility.description>This is the Overwatch Forward Reception Facility. After connecting mechanoids within range, they share with each other to strengthen defensive battles.</Overwatch_Forward_Receiving_Facility.description>

  <shield_system.label>shield system</shield_system.label>
  <shield_system.description>A shield capsule ejected by the Commander Drone. A shield made to protect allies. It is similar to a shield shield, but it has a short duration, so it must be used strategically.</shield_system.description>

  <Stim_Pack.label>mecha accelerator</Stim_Pack.label>
  <Stim_Pack.description>A mecha accelerator ejected by the Commander Drone. It enhances the combat power of all mechanoids, but it should be used with caution as it also enhances other mechanoids.</Stim_Pack.description>

  <location_detection_beacon.label>location detection beacon</location_detection_beacon.label>
  <location_detection_beacon.description>A detection beacon launched by a stealth drone. It exposes the location of the creature, but it also exposes the location of allies, so use it wisely.</location_detection_beacon.description>

  <spirit_stone_well.label>Spirit Stone Production Tower</spirit_stone_well.label>
  <spirit_stone_well.description>It is a kind of spirit tower that creates and produces spirit stones.\n\nThe spirit stone tower absorbs the floating unknown energy through the built-in spirit stone energy, converts it into a liquid form, and then converts it into a solid form to produce spirit stones. .\n\nHowever, whenever a spirit stone is produced, the pollution generated by the spirit stone is exported to the outer land during the disassembly process, so you must be prepared for contamination of the ground.</spirit_stone_well.description>

  <Frostsnow_table.label>Attribute Magic Workbench</Frostsnow_table.label>
  <Frostsnow_table.description>This is an attribute magic workbench.\n\nWeapons and other items made of fire and ice are made here.</Frostsnow_table.description>

  <ice_field.label>ice search</ice_field.label>
  <ice_field.description>After submerging it in the water, it disintegrates the stone bit by bit to find frozen ice shards.</ice_field.description>

  <ice_cutting_machine.label>ice cutting device</ice_cutting_machine.label>
  <ice_cutting_machine.description>A device that disassembles into stones to find ice fragments.</ice_cutting_machine.description>

  <recorder_table.label>record book</recorder_table.label>
  <recorder_table.description>It's a kind of record book that writes or records books, and it seems like a place where you just write ordinary books.. You can also make special books?.</recorder_table.description>

  <record_bookshelf.label>bookshelf</record_bookshelf.label>
  <record_bookshelf.description>A bookshelf is a collection of books containing various knowledge.</record_bookshelf.description>

  <constellation_observer.label>constellation generator</constellation_observer.label>
  <constellation_observer.description>It absorbs the energy flowing from the stars between the cosmic seas and produces electricity. This method only works over the night sky and does not work when the sun is up.</constellation_observer.description>


</LanguageData>