<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Hakuro.label>Hakuro</Hakuro.label>
  <Hakuro.description>Hakuro is a genotype with arctic wolf genes.\n\nA long time ago, it lived in industry, but was scattered by an some incident and was supposed to disappear silently while being hunted by those who called it the descendants of sanguophage. However, all that changed when they interacted with the passing races of machines. They gifted some of their technology to the White Wolves to research and develop various technologies, and let them live semi-living lives with genes called nanomaterials.\n\nNow, as several White Wolves go out into space, each faction While making , they went out into space and started to live on various planets, and even now, more several factions have been created.</Hakuro.description>
  <Hakuro.descriptionShort>Baekrang is a xenotype race with arctic wolf characteristics.\n\nThey mainly live in caves or mine resources, and they hunt instead of gardening. They excel at hunting and ranged, and eat less than other races through resection.</Hakuro.descriptionShort>
  <Hakuro_mine.label>Hakuro demon</Hakuro_mine.label>
  <Hakuro_mine.description>A race of hakuro born between a female vampire who abandoned as a result of a failed project long ago and a hakuro, \n\nThey have the characteristics of a vampire and a white wolf at the same time. But they are different from the vampires we know. They convert vampire powers and Hemera's nanomaterials into their own, which they use to support allies or obliterate enemies. For that reason, they were called witches or demons, and it is said that the squad destroyed by the staff and abilities they used on the battlefield.\n\nBut, unlike their evil appearance, they were calm when interacting with them or accepting them as settlers, and their mental Through solidarity, they can also become unbreakable lovers.</Hakuro_mine.description>
  <Hakuro_mine.descriptionShort>Hakuro demons are half-blooded xenos who inherited the genes of a vampire and a hakuro at the same time.\n\nThey are weak, but they are excellent in production, art, and gardening, growing blood flowers and making equipment, and using Hemera's abilities to Use to defeat enemies or assist allies.</Hakuro_mine.descriptionShort>
  <Hakuro_blood_knight.label>Hakuro blood</Hakuro_blood_knight.label>
  <Hakuro_blood_knight.description>They are a rare half-breed hakuro xenotype that is only born crazy for battle.\n\nThey are crazy enough to crave battle and like melee combat. THey has a slayer position that slaughters enemies standing in the vanguard, and uses not only hemera energy, but also the ability of blood to obliterate multiple enemies. Also use abilities to obliterate multiple enemies. However, they are also aware that they are violent not only to enemies but also to allies and have murderous conflicts, so they are staying away from themselves.</Hakuro_blood_knight.description>
  <Hakuro_blood_knight.descriptionShort>Blood is a rare mixed blood also a curse that occurred a long time ago. They are ordinary when they are young, but they gradually begin to reveal themselves, and as they become adults, their emotions slowly die, and eventually they become slayers themselves obsessed with slaughter. They are hardened and insensitive to pain, and attack indiscriminately with devastating melee abilities and blood essence that slashes enemies in seconds.</Hakuro_blood_knight.descriptionShort>
</LanguageData>