<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<packageId>RunningBugs.MRS.Hybrid</packageId>
	<name>More Raid Strategies: Hybrid Raids 更多的袭击类型：复合袭击</name>
	<author>RunningBugs</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.6</li>
	</supportedVersions>

	<modDependencies>
		<!-- <li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li> -->
	</modDependencies>

	<incompatibleWith>
		<!-- <li>username.modname</li> -->
	</incompatibleWith>

	<loadAfter>
		<!-- <li>username.modname</li> -->
	</loadAfter>

	<description>
The vanilla game has several raid types that we have been very familiar with, and in certain cases, we might want to try something different.
This mod is trying to add a few raid types that are hybrid of the vanilla raid types.
Warning: This could be hard, since we might have more frequent EdgeDrop raids, breaching raids, seige raids with breaching raids, etc.
This mod is the first in my planned "More Raid Strategies" series, we might try to add more different raid types in the form of other mods in the future.
Current implemented hybrid raids:
- Siege and Breach: A siege group (0.5 x points) and a breaching group (0.7 x points) attack at the same time
- Drop Pod and Breach: A drop-pod group (0.6 x points) and a breaching group (0.6 x points) attack at the same time


原版游戏的几种袭击类型，我们已经非常熟悉了，有时候，我们可能强的可怕，需要一些来自敌人的爱。
这个模组试图添加一些基于原版袭击类型的复合袭击类型。
警告：这可能会很难，因为我们可能会有更频繁的边缘掉落袭击、破门袭击，围攻配合破墙袭击等。
这个模组是我计划中的“更多袭击类型”系列中的第一个，在未来我们可能会在其他模组尝试添加更多不同的袭击类型。
当前实现的复合袭击类型：
- 围攻配合破墙：一个围攻小队（0.3 x 点数）和一个破墙小队（0.7 x 点数）同时攻击
- 掉落配合破墙：一个掉落小队（0.5 x 点数）和一个破墙小队（0.5 x 点数）同时攻击


It's possible not to use defs but to directly mix all in-game raid strategies (including modded ones) using C# code only.
The reason we don't go this approach is we might want more control over how the raids are mixed.
The downside is we have to manually configure each raid type we want to mix, unlike the pure C# code approach which can just generate all possible mixed types.

不使用XML Def，而是直接使用C#代码混合所有游戏内的袭击类型（包括模组添加的）是可行的。
我们不采用这种方法是为了更好地控制如何混合不同的袭击类型。
坏处是我们需要对每种想要复合的袭击类型进行手动配置。不像纯C#代码的方案可以直接生成所有可能的混合类型。

	</description>
</ModMetaData>
